PRIYANKA KHADANGA

Mumbai -8879074772

Email-priyankakhadanga9@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Goal-oriented recruiting professional with 1+ years of experience in Talent. Acquisition and HR Resources Recruiter role. Strong communication skill, motivated to achieve demanding targets under tight deadlines, Coordinating expertise with clients, candidates and team members, strong performer, problem-solver and administrator with focused and dedicated approach to meeting hiring needs.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 12th May 1995

? Gender: Female

Marital Status: Married

Hobbies: Dancing, Singing and Cooking

Language Proficiency: English, Hindi, Odisha & Marathi

EXPERIENCE

20th September, 2022- Till Date

<u>TALENT ACQUISITION ANALYST</u>, PROBIZ SOLUTIONS (Client Deutsache Bank)

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES: -

End to end candidate management throughout the recruitment process. Responsible for overall professional recruitment delivery for a specific business vertical. Experience in offer negotiations and offer management by interacting directly with the candidates and handholding them throughout the offer process, is a must.

• Develop and ensure adherence to the global recruitment policies, systems and procedures, including strategies and selection techniques. Implement

strategies to identify, attract and hire high quality talent

- Direct internal and external recruitment and placement activities of the company. Advises function heads and managers on Recruitment processes
- Establish and maintain relationships with Function heads / hiring managers to stay abreast of current and future hiring demand and forecast basis business needs
- Gather and analyse competitive industry information regarding salary, benefits, and employment practices (Market intelligence).
- Publish the weekly MIS to business on the hiring process. Good MS Excel skills.
- Engaging with India leadership team & Hiring Managers on strategic hiring mandates / projects, setting expectations & tracking progress
- Engaging with onshore hiring managers, guiding on India hiring processes / cultural nuances, setting expectations & tracking progress
- Managing 2nd level escalation cases & ensuring closures
- · Weekly team reviews on hiring mandates & progress made, challenges, etc.
- Weekly reviews with hiring managers on key recruitment mandates / strategic hiring. Provide market intelligence reports

EXPERIENCE

13th July, 2022- 13th October, 2022 (3 MONTHS)

HUMAN RESOURCE RECRUITER, MARS EXPLORATION PVT LTD

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES: -

Screening, shortlisting the candidate from different sources. Identifying future hiring needs and developing job descriptions and specifications.

Collaborating with department managers to compile a consistent list of requirements.

Attracting suitable candidates through databases, online employment forums, social media, etc.

Conducting interviews and sorting through applicants to fill open

positions.

Assessing applicants' knowledge, skills, and experience to best suit open positions.

Promoting the company's reputation and attractiveness as a good employment opportunity.

Managing internship programs.

Keeping up to date on current employment legislation and regulations and enforcing them within the company.

Providing recruitment reports to team managers.

21ST FEB 2022- 14th September, 2022

EDUCATION COUNCELLOR, SHARE KHAN

- **■** Accomplish sales goals
- **■** Build business by identifying and selling to prospective clients
- **■** Work closely with the solution team to ensure delivery of right solution to clients
- **■** Handover relationship to the relationship team
- For specific and defined clients: Maintaining relationship by ensuring support, information, and guidance using relevant back end teams

6TH APRIL'2017 – 7 TH OCTOBER'2021

STUDENT RELATIONSHIP EXECUTIVE, BOMBAY STOCK EXCHANGE INSTITUTE

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES: -

Monitor and identify clients and maintain client base through efficient interactions with clients and analyze any changes in client's needs.

Coordinate with prospects to understand individual client requirement and recommend plans to ensure achievement of all objectives.

Develop financial strategies and plans and recommend specific products to clients.

Develop and maintain relationship with business owners, individuals, corporate executives and influential personnel with client.

Supervise all finance sales process and manage multiple responsibilities.

Mange all communication with bank and provide excellent customer service and resolve any customer issues.

Administer all clients queries on financial issues manage effective resolution of all customer complaints.

Develop strategies to sell financial products like mutual funds, annuities, and insurance. Skilled in various computer programs in sales and marketing ·

Administer and access comprehensive personnel and business product lines. Great troubleshooting and problem-solving skills.

Assisted mid-level and senior sales representatives in managing client accounts, generating leads, and maintaining customer relationships.

Advise a client on whether to buy certain types of stocks, bonds and mutual funds. Develop financial strategies and plans and recommend specific products to clients. Prepare forms or agreements to complete sales.

7TH APRIL'16 – 30TH NOVEMBER'16 BACK OFFICE, GLOBAL HORIZON

KEY QUALIFICATIONS & RESPONSIBILITIES: -

- Created reports document results and analysis.
- Supervised and support research projects.
- ② Closely communicate with sales team to develop sales strategies.
- ② Utilized system databases to develop reports for forecasting and marketing trends. Ability to collaborate with team members or work independently.
- Provide face to face presentations to all the Corporate Sectors.

EDUCATION

MONTH YEAR DEGREE TITLE, SCHOOL

B HSC CBSE 2013 67%

- SSC CBSE 2011 78%MONTH YEAR 2020DEGREE TITLE, SCHOOL
- M.COM MUMBAI UNIVERSITY 72%
- BCOM MUMBAI UNIVERSITY 69%

SKILLS

- **EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION SKILL**
- 2 PROBLEM SOLVING SKILL
- **INNOVATIVE AND CREATIVE**
- **OPEN MINDED**
- **?** FLEXIBLE NATURE
- 2 PROACTIVE WORKER
- **WRITTEN AND VERBAL COMMUNICATION**
- PRESENTATION AND PUBLIC SPEAKING

Personal Qualities: -

- Punctuality
- Hard Working
- Quick Adaptability
- Sense of Responsibility

Core Qualifications

- 1. Candidate sourcing
- 2. Talent management
- 3. Benefits and compensation
- 4. Training and development
- 5. Recruitment
- 6. Cost
- 7. Wages and salary
- 8. Pre-employment screening
- 9. Benefits administrator
- 10. **1-2-1** counselling
- 11. Motivational mentorship
- 12. Performance assessments
- 13. Student progress analysis
- 14. Group instruction
- 15. Student motivation
- 16. Upselling expertise
- 17. Sales forecasting
- 18. Sales training
- 19. Hiring and training management

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Wow Card Certificate (Performer of the July 2020 Month)
- 2 Achieved target and performed well on daily and monthly basis
- Managed training and travel schedules and budgets for an organization Implemented a new CRM with reporting capabilities.
- ② Developed relationships with more than 1000 new clients and typically exceeded sales goals by 20%. Closed average 10-15 sales per day in outbound telemarketing
- Boosted new customer
- Successfully trained and coached more than 10 junior staff members Launching new products, projects or initiatives
- Solving a problem or challenge.
- Increasing the loyalty or satisfaction of existing customers

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above information is true & correct to the best of my Knowledge belief.

Date:

Place: Mumbai

(Priyanka Khadanga)